<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Daniel's Blog</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2020-05-22T20:43:50-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Daniel Yang</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Shirt Trading Database</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/16/Shirt-Trading/"/>
   <updated>2020-05-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2020/05/16/Shirt-Trading</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got a bit bored after getting 2/3 of the way through my AP exams, so I decided to just look into some SQL stuff. I created this simple form that handles inputs for my shirt trading addicti, I mean hobby. It’s really basic right now and since it’s hosted on GitHub Pages doesn’t work, but I thought I should show it off anyways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot more about SQL, databases, and php, while brushing up on some basic HTML. I created my first personal SQL server (it’s on a sketchy site, I know but none of this is important or sensetive) and got it working locally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;repository&quot;&gt;Repository&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/shirtTrading&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, while the live site (that doesn’t work) can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://danielyanger.github.io/shirtTrading/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a quick project that looks pretty bad. I plan to freshen it up a bit with CSS and add more features to make it more of a website. I plan to add a page where you can view my inventory (need to figure a way to do that on GitHub Pages or move to another free platform) and submit a trade request. Since it’s AP week, I don’t know when I’ll get back to it but we will see.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Learning Python</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/15/Python/"/>
   <updated>2020-04-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/15/Python</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the past few weeks, I’ve started to learn Python. I completed the Python 3 course on Code Academy as well as a couple of other courses related to Python.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that I am already proficient in Java, Python was not difficult to grasp. The syntax took a bit of getting used to and brushing off some of my Java habits took a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I know Python, I can start looking into more projects. Even though many of the things I want to do could be done in Java, I want to continue to push myself and improve my Python skills.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Learning React</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/27/Learning-React/"/>
   <updated>2020-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/27/Learning-React</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With more time on my hands due to the COVID-19 outbreak, I took the opportunity to learn more about programming. One of the first things I learned about was React. I followed a simple YouTube tutorial that guided me through setting up and using React.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first project that used React and I learned a lot about how it works. Making the simple counters using React was very different compared to JavaScript, which I have done in the past. While it was definitely more complicated to due this simple task, the applications for it are numerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository for the project is located &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/Intro-to-React&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. I didn’t create it as a repository and uploaded it afterwards so there isn’t a history to the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the end of this project as I don’t plan to do too much else with it. It was a fun first delve into React and a refresher about HTML, CSS, and web design. While I may not be using React for a while, it was definitely a great experience.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Programming Curriculum</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/25/Programming-Curriculum/"/>
   <updated>2020-03-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/25/Programming-Curriculum</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the cancellation of the 2020 FRC Season and the subsequent postponement of school, I decided to take this opportunity to revamp our team’s programming curriculum. I created 9 different levels split into 3 categories: Basic, Intermediate, and Advanced. Each level is designed to teach incoming programmers about LabVIEW and coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the development of this curriculum, I learned a lot about preparing teaching materials and lessons. Each level started with a lesson plan that had objectives, resources, and homework. Some of the lessons then required a presentation to be created while others did not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;google-drive&quot;&gt;Google Drive&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The link to the curriculum can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=12C09_11jrvME_3CtKL9LgwKkSNhXsidO&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since next year will be my senior year, I plan to utilize this curriculum to teach the next batch of programmers. I also plan to refine the curriculum as the year progress in hopes that it can be passed on to the next generation of Team 624 programmers.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Academic Decathlon State Results</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/08/Acadec-State/"/>
   <updated>2020-03-08T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/08/Acadec-State</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;state&quot;&gt;State&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Update time! This past weekend I competed in San Antonio with my Academic Decathlon team. At state, I once again placed in both math and speech. This time however, I score a perfect 1000 on math and was 2nd in speech, both improvements to my regional results. Additionally, we placed 6th overall in Super Quiz and were ranked 7th in the state for large schools. I’m really proud of both my team’s results and my own and can’t wait to see our improvements next year.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Academic Decathlon Regionals Results</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/02/08/Acadec/"/>
   <updated>2020-02-08T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2020/02/08/Acadec</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;regionals&quot;&gt;Regionals&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event was very exciting for me as it was my first official competition with my school’s Academic Decathlon team. Our team performed very well, placing second in Super Quiz and 3rd overall. Individually, I also placed 2nd overall in math and 3rd overall in speech. Furthermore, I was my team’s highest individual score with a 8,524.1 out of 10,000. We have also qualified for state with is a couple of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>USACO December 2019</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/12/14/USACO-Programming/"/>
   <updated>2019-12-14T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2019/12/14/USACO-Programming</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;bronze&quot;&gt;Bronze&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was my first attempt at USACO. Prior to this, I had very little exposure to competitive programming. I relied mainly on my Java knowledge from AP Computer Science A to get me through. Since it was my first time, I was in the bronze division. I scored a 1000 on my first attempt, giving me a promotion into Silver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to continue to participate in USACO. Due to the robotics season starting up very shortly, I will have little time to practice and prepare for Silver. However, I will try my best throughout all of the competitions.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>New Personal Website</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/08/25/Website/"/>
   <updated>2019-08-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2019/08/25/Website</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After putting my blog on a Weebly site for a while, I’ve decided to start transitioning over to a GitHub Pages and try and get everything onto GitHub. Over the next few months, I’ll be adding in posts to try and make sure everything was covered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By switching over to a GitHub Pages, I’ve learned a lot about Ruby, Jekyll, and Git. I hadn’t used much Git prior to this and definitely need work on it but this is a good place to start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Git Project can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/danielyanger.github.io&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope to continue to improve the website by adding in previous blog posts as well as updating it with new posts. I’ll continue development on it for at least the foreseeable future.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>AP Statistics Score</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/11/AP-Stats/"/>
   <updated>2019-07-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/11/AP-Stats</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;ap&quot;&gt;AP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With my second year of AP scores in, I am proud that I earned a 5 on my AP Stats exam. Since this is my programming blog, I’ll only post AP scores that are related to programming (so math and computer science). Cheers to more 5s!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Impulse Robot Code</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/04/25/Impulse-Robot-Code/"/>
   <updated>2019-04-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2019/04/25/Impulse-Robot-Code</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the code for my robotics team’s 2019 robot, Impulse. Impulse is once again coded in LabVIEW. This was my second year on the programming subteam and took on more responsibilities. I was in charge of the development of autonomous routines for our robot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I continued to improve upon my LabVIEW skills this year, learning a lot more about the FRC framework. I also learned how to use Isotope, our team’s custom autonomous routine writer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository for the project is not currently public but if the code is released, I will post an update.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the end of this project as the 2019 FRC season comes to a close. Next year will be my junior year and I will be taking on even more responsibilities in regards to programming. The current lead programmer is graduating so I will be stepping up in the amount I am programming. Can’t wait for next year!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Eagle Scout Update</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/19/Eagle-Scout-Update/"/>
   <updated>2019-02-19T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/19/Eagle-Scout-Update</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;update&quot;&gt;Update&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though this is not related to programming, I thought that it was important nonetheless. Today I completed my Eagle Scout Board of Review and officially became an Eagle Scout. After four and a half years of hard work, dozens of nights spent camping, and countless miles hiked, I have finally reached the top.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Scouting Whitepaper</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/07/Scouting-WP/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/07/Scouting-WP</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this is not completely programming related, this was my first ever white paper. Our team has long relies on using either paper or pencil scouting or using personal devices to scout. However, with this white paper I was able to convince the board to invest $2000 into new equipment to help our team scout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through writing and editing this white paper, I improved my persuasive writing techniques. It also allowed me to better understand project constraints as I had to envision and work within a defined budget to achieve our goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;white-paper&quot;&gt;White Paper&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The white paper can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Q4UFuG-9-dFI42fBowHwvH9mJ2_imZaYjWjXiaBfhoo/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. This was the same version that was submitted to the board and approved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the approval of my proposal, we are moving forward with the current deployment of our new equipment. We have been developing an app that will be optimized for the tablets and allow us to utilize our new resources.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Start of my Programming Blog</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/15/Blog/"/>
   <updated>2018-10-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/15/Blog</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve decided to create a website/blog to host all of the programming related things that I’ve done and will be doing through high school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now I’ll keep the blog on this Weebly site but I may look to transition over to another platform in the future as an exercise in programming.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Team Blog</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/09/08/Team-Blog/"/>
   <updated>2018-09-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/09/08/Team-Blog</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, our team started using a private blog to keep track of the hours our members put into the team. As a sophomore, I was put in charge of maintaining the site and dealing with any issues that students encountered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through my role as the webmaster of the blog, I used a lot of SQL to reference data stored on the team server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, once again, the code to our blog is private and the site is password protected. I will attach some photos of the site below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving forward, the team plans to continue using the blog. As the webmaster of the blog, I plan to continue to improve the blog and add features that will aid the team.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Eagle Scout Project</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/23/Eagle-Scout-Project/"/>
   <updated>2018-07-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/07/23/Eagle-Scout-Project</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I completed my Eagle Scout Project. For my project, I partnered with SEWA International to deliver a STEM and Programming camp to underprivileged children in the Greater Houston Area. I had many different stations for the children to experience, including making ice cream, bottle rockets, and intro to programming. The kids had a blast and loved the camp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;documentation&quot;&gt;Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I have carefully documented everything, I am unable to publish it on the internet. Many of my documents contain personal information that cannot be published. However, if you are interested in it, feel free to send me an email and we can discuss potential ways for you to view them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With my project now done, I have almost earned my Eagle Scout rank. Most of the work remaining is paperwork and meetings so I expect to earn it soon. In terms of the camp, I know many other scouts who are interesting in hosting a similar camp so I will be mentoring them and providing guidance to them.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>AP Computer Science Score</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/15/AP-Comp_Sci/"/>
   <updated>2018-07-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/07/15/AP-Comp_Sci</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;ap&quot;&gt;AP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just wanted to post an update that I earned a 5 on my AP Computer Science A exam. It was overall an easy exam so I felt confident about getting a 5. That said, I am still proud of myself and this was my first every AP exam.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Team 624 Main Website</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/06/02/Website/"/>
   <updated>2018-06-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/06/02/Website</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is project was my second major project involving website development, the first being the scouting website. This was our main site that was visible to the public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first website project that involved images and more website CSS elements. I learned about website design as well as fine-tuned my skills in HTML and CSS. Furthermore, I was exposed to PHP for the first time as that was the language the website was built upon at the time and how to communicate with the SQL server. I also learned about PuTTY and how to SSH into the website to push changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the code to our main website is not available to the public. However, you can view the work at &lt;a href=&quot;http://team624.org/&quot;&gt;team624.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just the start to my work on the site. Over the next 3 years, I will continue to maintain the site and update it as need be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;update-september-2019&quot;&gt;Update September 2019&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After much deliberation, the team has elected to move our website to WordPress. &lt;a href=&quot;http://team624.org/&quot;&gt;Team624.org&lt;/a&gt; will no longer be maintained. The new site can be found at &lt;a href=&quot;http://frc624.org/&quot;&gt;frc624.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>2018 FRC Power Up Robot Code</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/04/25/Power-Up-Robot/"/>
   <updated>2018-04-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/04/25/Power-Up-Robot</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the code for my robotics team’s 2018 robot, PaCRat. PaCRat is coded in LabVIEW. This was my first year on the programming subteam and my first exposure to LabVIEW. As a graphical language, it was very different from other text based languages that I had been learning about such as HTML or Java.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first project that used LabVIEW. Additionally, I learned a lot about hardware integration while programming the robot, such as using encoders, motor controllers, and various sensors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository for the project is located &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Team624/2018Robot&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. As a freshman and novice programmer, I did most of my testing on separate branches that were later merged onto the master branch by senior programmers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the end of this project as the 2018 FRC season comes to a close. However, I have 3 more years of robotics left in high school so there will be 3 more robots left to program. Looking forward to these new challenges!&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>624 Scouting Website</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/15/Scouting-Website/"/>
   <updated>2018-01-15T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/15/Scouting-Website</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my first project that I am working on with my robotics team, FRC Team 624. We are creating a website to host our scouting system. The purpose of this system is to allow students to quickly and easily input data about the performance of robots during a match. It then stores that data on a SQL server for data analysis to determine which team which should pick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot of useful skills through this project including CSS, HTML, and JavaScript. I worked on mostly the design of certain modules within the site. I used JavaScript to make integer incriminators and zebra striped, sortable tables. This was also my first introduction to Git and version control, something I can definitely improve on as I continue working on the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the code to our scouting database is not available to the public. However, I will try and include some images of my work below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope to continue to adapt the site as we refine our scouting system. Since I am only a freshman, I have 3 more years on this team and each year requiring an update to this website.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
