<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-29T21:24:35-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Daniel’s Blog</title><subtitle>Welcome to my programming blog! I have plenty of posts about my programming (and some non-programming) achievements.</subtitle><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><entry><title type="html">Learning Node</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/15/Node-JS/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learning Node" /><published>2020-06-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-06-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/15/Node-JS</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/15/Node-JS/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With summer in full swing and a realitivly light course load for summer school, I took this oppurtunity to start learning Node.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this project, I learned a great deal about Node JS, APIs, and Express JS. Furthermore, it was a refresher in JavaScript for me after not using it for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/Learning-Node&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I have learned Node, I plan to freshen up a bit on React and then become a full stack developer! Stay tuned for that.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">624 Scouting Manager</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/04/Scouting-Manager/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="624 Scouting Manager" /><published>2020-06-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-06-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/04/Scouting-Manager</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/04/Scouting-Manager/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of my overhaul of my team’s scouting system, I have made a Windows Form that will link the different apps and merge the files.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through this project, I dipped my toes into C# and made a Windows Form in Visual Studio. Additionally, I learned how to make API calls in python and how to properly parse through a JSON file in python.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/624-Scouting-Manager&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to continue to work on the project and finish debugging it in preparation for next season.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New 624 Scouting App</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/31/Scouting-App/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New 624 Scouting App" /><published>2020-05-31T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-05-31T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/05/31/Scouting-App</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/31/Scouting-App/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the time between the end of AP exams and the start of summer school, I decided to create a new scouting app for my robotics team. Following the approval of my proposal for new tabelts, our team started using an app called Roblu for scouting. However, I wanted to build a system from the group up tailored for our team. One issue we had while using Roblue was regarding the use of Bluetooth to transmit data. While sometimes it worked, othertimes it would seem to lose data. This is a huge issue so I decided to instead have it export to local files and then use a python script to merge the data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first time using Flutter so I learned a lot about both flutter and dart. I picked it up very quickly and in only 2 days, created a system where you can dynamically generate forms using the master app. This allows the system to be used by a head scout even if they have no programming experience. This is crucial to the success of the scouting team. Additionally, I plan to create a couple of python scripts and incorporate them with a C# Windows Form to create an all in one package for the team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The projects are currently not visible to the public but this status could change in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to continue to refine the app and fix any bugs. Right now I plan to start creating the Python scripts to unite all the aspects of the two apps.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Shirt Trading Database</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/16/Shirt-Trading/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shirt Trading Database" /><published>2020-05-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-05-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/05/16/Shirt-Trading</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/16/Shirt-Trading/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got a bit bored after getting 2/3 of the way through my AP exams, so I decided to just look into some SQL stuff. I created this simple form that handles inputs for my shirt trading addiction, I mean hobby. It’s really basic right now and since it’s hosted on GitHub Pages doesn’t work, but I thought I should show it off anyways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot more about SQL, databases, and php, while brushing up on some basic HTML. I created my first personal SQL server (it’s on a sketchy site, I know but none of this is important or sensitive) and got it working locally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;repository&quot;&gt;Repository&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/shirtTrading&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, while the live site (that doesn’t work) can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://danielyanger.github.io/shirtTrading/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a quick project that looks pretty bad. I plan to freshen it up a bit with CSS and add more features to make it more of a website. I plan to add a page where you can view my inventory (need to figure a way to do that on GitHub Pages or move to another free platform) and submit a trade request. Since it is AP week, I don’t know when I’ll get back to it but we will see.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Project Page</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/04/Project-Page/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Page" /><published>2020-05-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-05-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/05/04/Project-Page</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/04/Project-Page/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the switch to the Hyde theme for my blog, I decided that I wanted to have a page where all my blog posts were visible. So I coded it in as a seperate page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through this adventure of figuring out how to program this, I learned more about Liquid and HTML to code this in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/danielyanger.github.io&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With AP exams right around the corner, I won’t be doing much more development on the site. I really like how it is set up right now and will probably leave it be for a while.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Website Theme</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/30/Website-Theme/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Website Theme" /><published>2020-04-30T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-04-30T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/30/Website-Theme</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/30/Website-Theme/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a bit of testing, I have finally implemented the Hyde theme for my personal blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through this adventure of figuring out the theme issues, I was able to learn more about many different things, including Git and Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/danielyanger.github.io&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like this theme so I’ll probably stick with it for a while. I might add a page where all of my posts are visible since I did like that from my previous theme.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pong</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/20/Pong/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pong" /><published>2020-04-20T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-04-20T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/20/Pong</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/20/Pong/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I know the basics of Python, I decided to apply some of what I learned and create a quick game of Pong. This Pong game gradually speeds up as the game progresses, making it more and more challenging the longer the rally is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to improving my basic Python knowledge, I learned about the Python library Turtles and random. Both of these were useful in creating the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/Python-Projects/blob/master/pong.py&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to continue to create small Python projects to improve my python knowledge but with AP exams coming up, I may not have much time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Learning Python</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/15/Python/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learning Python" /><published>2020-04-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-04-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/15/Python</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/15/Python/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the past few weeks, I’ve started to learn Python. I completed the Python 3 course on Code Academy as well as a couple of other courses related to Python.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that I am already proficient in Java, Python was not difficult to grasp. The syntax took a bit of getting used to and brushing off some of my Java habits took a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I know Python, I can start looking into more projects. Even though many of the things I want to do could be done in Java, I want to continue to push myself and improve my Python skills.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Learning React</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/27/Learning-React/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learning React" /><published>2020-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/27/Learning-React</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/27/Learning-React/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With more time on my hands due to the COVID-19 outbreak, I took the opportunity to learn more about programming. One of the first things I learned about was React. I followed a simple YouTube tutorial that guided me through setting up and using React.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first project that used React and I learned a lot about how it works. Making the simple counters using React was very different compared to JavaScript, which I have done in the past. While it was definitely more complicated to due this simple task, the applications for it are numerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository for the project is located &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/Intro-to-React&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. I didn’t create it as a repository and uploaded it afterwards so there isn’t a history to the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the end of this project as I don’t plan to do too much else with it. It was a fun first delve into React and a refresher about HTML, CSS, and web design. While I may not be using React for a while, it was definitely a great experience.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Programming Curriculum</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/25/Programming-Curriculum/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Programming Curriculum" /><published>2020-03-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-03-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/25/Programming-Curriculum</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/25/Programming-Curriculum/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the cancellation of the 2020 FRC Season and the subsequent postponement of school, I decided to take this opportunity to revamp our team’s programming curriculum. I created 9 different levels split into 3 categories: Basic, Intermediate, and Advanced. Each level is designed to teach incoming programmers about LabVIEW and coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the development of this curriculum, I learned a lot about preparing teaching materials and lessons. Each level started with a lesson plan that had objectives, resources, and homework. Some of the lessons then required a presentation to be created while others did not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;google-drive&quot;&gt;Google Drive&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The link to the curriculum can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=12C09_11jrvME_3CtKL9LgwKkSNhXsidO&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since next year will be my senior year, I plan to utilize this curriculum to teach the next batch of programmers. I also plan to refine the curriculum as the year progress in hopes that it can be passed on to the next generation of Team 624 programmers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry></feed>