<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-22T20:30:50-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Daniel’s Blog</title><subtitle>Welcome to my programming blog! I have plenty of posts about my programming (and some non-programming) achievements.</subtitle><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><entry><title type="html">Shirt Trading Database</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/16/Shirt-Trading/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Shirt Trading Database" /><published>2020-05-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-05-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/05/16/Shirt-Trading</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/16/Shirt-Trading/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got a bit bored after getting 2/3 of the way through my AP exams, so I decided to just look into some SQL stuff. I created this simple form that handles inputs for my shirt trading addicti, I mean hobby. It’s really basic right now and since it’s hosted on GitHub Pages doesn’t work, but I thought I should show it off anyways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot more about SQL, databases, and php, while brushing up on some basic HTML. I created my first personal SQL server (it’s on a sketchy site, I know but none of this is important or sensetive) and got it working locally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;repository&quot;&gt;Repository&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/shirtTrading&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, while the live site (that doesn’t work) can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://danielyanger.github.io/shirtTrading/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a quick project that looks pretty bad. I plan to freshen it up a bit with CSS and add more features to make it more of a website. I plan to add a page where you can view my inventory (need to figure a way to do that on GitHub Pages or move to another free platform) and submit a trade request. Since it’s AP week, I don’t know when I’ll get back to it but we will see.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Learning React</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/27/Learning-React/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learning React" /><published>2020-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-03-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/27/Learning-React</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/27/Learning-React/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With more time on my hands due to the COVID-19 outbreak, I took the oppurtunity to learn more about programming. One of the first things I learned about was React. I followed a simple YouTube tutorial that guided me through setting up and using React.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first project that used React and I learned a lot about how it works. Making the simple counters using React was very different compared to JavaScript, which I have done in the past. While it was definitely more complicated to due this simple task, the applications for it are numerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository for the project is located &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DanielYanger/Intro-to-React&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. I didn’t create it as a repository and uploaded it afterwards so there isn’t a history to the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the end of this project as I don’t plan to do too much else with it. It was a fun first delve into React and a refresher about HTML, CSS, and web design. While I may not be using React for a while, it was definetly a great experience.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Programming Curriculum</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/25/Programming-Curriculum/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Programming Curriculum" /><published>2020-03-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-03-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/25/Programming-Curriculum</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/25/Programming-Curriculum/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the cancellation of the 2020 FRC Season and the subsequent postponement of school, I deceided to take this oppurtunity to revamp our team’s programming curriculum. I created 9 different levels split into 3 categories: Basic, Intermediate, and Advanced. Each level is designed to teach incoming programers about LabVIEW and coding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the development of this curriulum, I learned a lot about preparing teaching materials and lessons. Each level started with a lesson plan that had objectives, resources, and homework. Some of the lessons then required a presentation to be created while others did not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;google-drive&quot;&gt;Google Drive&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The link to the curriculum can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=12C09_11jrvME_3CtKL9LgwKkSNhXsidO&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since next year will be my senior year, I plan to utilize this curriculum to teach the next batch of programmers. I also plan to refine the curriculum as the year progress in hopes that it can be passed on to the next generation of Team 624 programmers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">USACO December 2019</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/12/14/USACO-Programming/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="USACO December 2019" /><published>2019-12-14T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-12-14T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/12/14/USACO-Programming</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/12/14/USACO-Programming/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;bronze&quot;&gt;Bronze&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was my first attempt at USACO. Prior to this, I had very little exposure to competative programming. I relied mainly on my Java knowledge from AP Computer Science A to get me through. Since it was my first time, I was in the bronze division. I scored a 1000 on my first attempt, giving me a promotion into Silver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to continue to participate in USACO. Due to the robotics season starting up very shortly, I will have little time to practice and prepare for Silver. However, I will try my best throughout all of the competitions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Bronze</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AP Statistics Score</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/11/AP-Stats/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AP Statistics Score" /><published>2019-07-11T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-07-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/11/AP-Stats</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/11/AP-Stats/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;ap&quot;&gt;AP&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With my second year of AP scores in, I am proud that I earned a 5 on my AP Stats exam. Since this is my programming blog, I’ll only post AP scores that are related to programming (so math and computer science). Cheers to more 5s!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">AP</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Impulse Robot Code</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/04/25/Impulse-Robot-Code/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Impulse Robot Code" /><published>2019-04-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/04/25/Impulse-Robot-Code</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/04/25/Impulse-Robot-Code/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the code for my robotics team’s 2019 robot, Impulse. Impulse is once again coded in LabVIEW. This was my second year on the programming subteam and took on more responsiblities. I was in charge of the development of autonmous routines for our robot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I continued to improve upon my LabVIEW skills this year, learning a lot more about the FRC framework. I also learned how to use Isotope, our team’s custom autonomous routine writer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository for the project is not currently public but if the code is released, I will post an update.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the end of this project as the 2019 FRC season comes to a close. Next year will be my junior year and I will be taking on even more responsiblities in regards to programming. The current lead programmer is graduating so I will be stepping up in the amount I am programming. Can’t wait for next year!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Scouting Whitepaper</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/25/Scouting-App/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Scouting Whitepaper" /><published>2019-02-25T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-02-25T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/25/Scouting-App</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/25/Scouting-App/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this is not completely programming related, this was my first ever white paper. Our team has long relies on using either paper and pencil scouting or using personal devices to scout. However, with this white paper I was able to convince the board to invest $2000 into new equipment to help our team scout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through writing and editing this white paper, I improved my persuasive writing techniques. It also allowed me to better understand project constraints as I had to envision and work within a defined budget to achieve our goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;white-paper&quot;&gt;White Paper&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The white paper can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Q4UFuG-9-dFI42fBowHwvH9mJ2_imZaYjWjXiaBfhoo/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. This was the same version that was submitted to the board and approved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the approval of my proposal, we are moving forward with the current deployment of our new equipment. We have been developing an app that will be optimized for the tablets and allow us to utilize our new resources.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Eagle Scout Update</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/19/Eagle-Scout-Update/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Eagle Scout Update" /><published>2019-02-19T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-02-19T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/19/Eagle-Scout-Update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/19/Eagle-Scout-Update/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;update&quot;&gt;Update&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though this is not related to programming, I thought that it was important nonetheless. Today I completed my Eagle Scout Board of Review and offically became an Eagle Scout. After four and a half years of hard work, dozens of nights spent camping, and countless miles hiked, I have finally reached the top.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Update</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Scouting Whitepaper</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/07/Scouting-WP/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Scouting Whitepaper" /><published>2018-12-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-12-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/07/Scouting-WP</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/07/Scouting-WP/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this is not completely programming related, this was my first ever white paper. Our team has long relies on using either paper and pencil scouting or using personal devices to scout. However, with this white paper I was able to convince the board to invest $2000 into new equipment to help our team scout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through writing and editing this white paper, I improved my persuasive writing techniques. It also allowed me to better understand project constraints as I had to envision and work within a defined budget to achieve our goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;white-paper&quot;&gt;White Paper&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The white paper can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Q4UFuG-9-dFI42fBowHwvH9mJ2_imZaYjWjXiaBfhoo/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. This was the same version that was submitted to the board and approved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the approval of my proposal, we are moving forward with the current deployment of our new equipment. We have been developing an app that will be optimized for the tablets and allow us to utilize our new resources.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Team Blog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/09/08/Team-Blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Team Blog" /><published>2018-09-08T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-09-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/09/08/Team-Blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/09/08/Team-Blog/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year, our team started using a private blog to keep track of the hours our members put into the team. As a sophomore, I was put in charge of maintaining the site and dealing with any issues that students encountered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through my role as the webmaster of the blog, I used a lot of SQL to reference data stored on the team server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, once again, the code to our blog is private and the site is password protected. I will attach some photos of the site below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving forward, the team plans to continue using the blog. As the webmaster of the blog, I plan to continue to improve the blog and add features that will aid the team.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Daniel Yang</name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry></feed>