<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-02T23:05:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Daniel Yang’s Programming Blog</title><subtitle>Hello! My name is Daniel Yang and I am a student at Cinco Ranch High School in Katy, Texas. I have a passion for computer science and programming. This is my programming blog where I post about what I am doing in programming. I plan to post whatever projects I have completed and some updates on current projects.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Team 624 Main Website</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/06/02/Website.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Team 624 Main Website" /><published>2018-06-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-06-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/06/02/Website</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/06/02/Website.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is project was my second major project involving website development, the first being the scouting website. This was our main site that was visible to the public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first website project that involved images and more website CSS elements. I learned about website design as well as fine tuned my skills in HTML and CSS. Furthermore, I was exposed to PHP for the first time as that was the language the website was built upon at the time and how to communicate with the SQL server. I also learned about PuTTY and how to SSH into the website to push changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the code to our main website is not avalible to the public. However, you can view the work at &lt;a href=&quot;http://team624.org/&quot;&gt;team624.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just the start to my work on the site. Over the next 3 years, I will continue to maintain the site and update it as need be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;update-september-2019&quot;&gt;Update September 2019&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After much deliberation, the team has elected to move our website to Wordpress. &lt;a href=&quot;http://team624.org/&quot;&gt;Team624.org&lt;/a&gt; will no longer be maintained. The new site can be found at &lt;a href=&quot;http://frc624.org/&quot;&gt;frc624.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2018 FRC Power Up Robot Code</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/04/25/Power-Up-Robot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2018 FRC Power Up Robot Code" /><published>2018-04-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-04-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/04/25/Power-Up-Robot</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/04/25/Power-Up-Robot.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the code for my robotics team’s 2018 robot, PaCRat. PaCRat is coded in LabVIEW. This was my first year on the programming subteam and my first exposure to LabVIEW. As a graphical language, it was very different from other text based languages that I had been learning about such as HTML or Java.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first project that used LabVIEW. Additiionally, I learned a lot about hardware integration while programming the robot, such as using encoders, motor controllers, and various sensors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository for the project is located &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Team624/2018Robot&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. As a freshman and noivce programmer, I did most of my testing on seperate branches that were later merged onto the master branch by senior programmers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the end of this project as the 2018 FRC season comes to a close. However, I have 3 more years of robotics left in high school so there will be 3 more robots left to program. Looking forward to these new challenges!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">624 Scouting Website</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/15/Scouting-Website.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="624 Scouting Website" /><published>2018-01-15T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-01-15T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/15/Scouting-Website</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/15/Scouting-Website.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my first project that I am working on with my robotics team, FRC Team 624. We are creating a website to host our scouting system. The purpose of this system is to allow students to quickly and easily input data about the performace of robots during a match. It then stores that data on a SQL server for data analysis to determine which team which should pick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;skills&quot;&gt;Skills&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned a lot of useful skills through this project including php, CSS, HTML, and Javascript. I worked on mostly the design of certain modules within the site. I used Javascript to make integer incrementors and zebra striped, sortable tables. This was also my first introduction to Git and version control, something I can defenitly improve on as I continue working on the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;git-project&quot;&gt;Git Project&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the code to our scouting database is not avalible to the public. However, I will try and include some images of my work below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;moving-forward&quot;&gt;Moving Forward&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope to continue to adapt the site as we refine our scouting system. Since I am only a freshman, I have 3 more years on this team and each year requiring an update to this website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction</summary></entry></feed>